Pavel Skuratovets

JAVA SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

pavelstj@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/pavelstj Minsk, Belarus

PROFILE

Software engineer with an ability to adapt, work persistently and concentrate. Develop backend in Java, work with a relational database, have experience in frontend with React/Redux. My goal is to increase the level of English and my technical skills and to improve the results of work.

PROJECTS

Logistic automatic system

08/2021 - 10/2022

Warehouse manager with the ability to order the necessary goods easily, check information about your orders, track them, control the return of items.

Resource Balancing System

12/2020 - 01/2021

A system designated for automating staffing optimization processes at production lines of a major plant. It allows to organize and register staff transfers between production sections, to optimize vacation plans etc.

Musical Fountain System

02/2020 - 08/2020

A system designated for operating Brest musical fountain. It allows ordering shows via SMS, controlling the fountain, tracing its status and collecting measurements at the fountain's equiment.

Auditor Certification

08/2019 - 12/2019, 08/2020 - 08/2021

Auditor certification system for the Ministry of Finance of the Republic of Belarus. The system is designated for conducing different types of exams (automatic, oral, mixed) and for the support of all internal business processes (dictionaries, report and document generation, statistics etc)

PRO SKILLS

Java Hibernate
SQL, PL/pgSQL MapStruct
PostgreSQL Gradle

Spring Framework Git

Spring Data REST API
Spring Web Docker

Spring Security Apache Maven

口

П

PERSONAL SKILLS

Adaptability

Team Work

Hard Work

Problem-solving

EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

Solbeg - Minsk, Belarus

08/2021 - 10/2022

Junior Software Developer

Epol Soft - Brest, Belarus

08/2019 - 08/2021

EDUCATION

Industrial electronics Brest State Technical University 09/2015 - 07/2019

LANGUAGES

English - A2+

Russian - native